visabusinessnetwork.com 2010-09-27

# The Visa Business Network

Updated July 2010

Any time you visit a Web site, you may be providing information about yourself to the Web site's owner or operator. We at Visa Inc. ("Visa", "we", "us" or "our"), like you, value privacy, so we want you to learn what you need to know to protect your personal privacy. When you visit or supply information to any Web site, it's a good idea for you to first understand the Web site's privacy policies. If the Web site owner doesn't tell you, don't hesitate to ask. 

The bottom line at the Visa Business Network (the "VBN") is that we use information that we get from your visit to enable you to participate in and take advantage of the various programs and features presented on the VBN, for our own internal analysis, to make the VBN and our programs and features more useful and interesting to you, and to let you know about products, services, and opportunities from Visa, our partners, issuers, and merchants that may be of interest to you as a member of the VBN. We do not share your personal information that we collect through the VBN with any affiliate or third party, except as specifically noted, and with agencies, vendors, licensors, partners, or affiliates under contract with Visa. 

##### A special note about children

The VBN is not intended for users under the age of 18, and VBN does not knowingly collect personal information from those users. 

##### About the Visa Business Network

The VBN is comprised of: (i) a website located at www.visabusinessnetwork.com (the "VBN Website"), and (ii) an application within the Facebook Platform (the "VBN Facebook Application"). Both the VBN Website and the VBN Facebook Application are subject to the VBN Terms of Use, which can be found at www.visabusinessnetwork.com/about/terms_and_conditions and/or <http://apps.facebook.com/visabusiness/about/terms_and_conditions>. The VBN Facebook Application is also subject to Facebook policies, including the Facebook Terms of Use <http://www.facebook.com/terms.php>, and the [Facebook Platform Application Terms of Use](http://developers.facebook.com/user_terms.php). and and your use of Twitter-related functions is also subject to Twitter policies, including the [Twitter Terms of Service](http://twitter.com/tos) and the [Twitter Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy). In the event of conflicting or inconsistent provisions, the VBN Terms of Use control. 

When you register for the VBN, the personal information you submit in registering for the VBN is separate from any personal information you submit in connection with registration on third-party sites, including your Facebook or Twitter account, profile or any other third-party applications, or any information you submit via any websites outside the VBN. 

Note that notwithstanding anything else contained herein, the VBN will display personal information submitted as part of your VBN profile and other data related to your use of the VBN in accordance with your VBN privacy settings and/or your privacy settings for any third-party websites or applications, as applicable. For example, your addition of the VBN Facebook Application to your Facebook account will be displayed on your Facebook profile and other Facebook pages (which may also include third-party websites to which Facebook provides content through plug-ins or other devices, including through Facebook Connect) unless, in your Facebook privacy settings, you opt out of displaying the VBN Facebook Application on your other Facebook pages. If you do not specifically opt out from such disclosures, you authorize the display of the VBN Applications and resulting information on third-party website profiles and other pages. 

The following portions of your VBN profile will be available via the public Internet: your business name, business type, and ZIP code. Other portions of your VBN profile may be available to the public Internet depending on your VBN privacy settings. Other than your business name, business type and ZIP code, you may opt-out of displaying portions of your VBN profile by editing your VBN privacy settings, however we do not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their cache. 

##### Applicability of this privacy policy

This privacy policy applies only to the personal information that you disclose or submit through the VBN. This privacy policy does not apply to any personal information you submit to Facebook outside the VBN Facebook Application, and/or any information you submit via any websites outside the VBN. It also does not apply to information that Visa collects through other websites or locations, including other Visa websites or websites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors, partners, issuers, or merchants. When visiting Facebook pages outside the VBN Facebook Application, Visa websites other than the VBN Website, and/or any other website, please review the privacy policy for those websites for details on how personal information is collected, used and shared. 

On this page: 

##### NOTICE

  * Types of Information Collected on the Visa Business Network
  * Browsing and the use of Google Analytics
  * Sweepstakes, contests, games, and surveys
  * Email, mailing lists, and other services
  * Affiliated businesses and links to other sites
  * Our policy regarding selling or renting of personal information
  * Agents, Partners, and Vendors
  * Banners and other advertisements on VBN
  * Business transfers
  * Disclosure of personal information for legal purposes and protection of Visa and others

##### CHOICE

  * How you can decide what messages you'll receive from us

##### ACCESS AND DATA RETENTION

  * How to update, correct, or delete your personal information

##### SECURITY

  * How we protect the security of your personal information

##### CUSTOMER SERVICE AND RECOURSE

  * Changes to the Visa Business Network privacy policy
  * How to contact Visa regarding your concerns and questions

#### NOTICE

##### Types of Information Collected on the Visa Business Network

Visa collects two types of data: (1) personal and business information you submit to us in connection with registering and using the VBN; and (2) information about your use of the VBN collected through the use of web technology. 

Personal and Business Information

When you register with the VBN, you provide certain personal information and information concerning you and your business that identifies or can be used to identify you or your business, including your name, your business' name, your and/or your business' email address, telephone number, your and/or your business' address, your gender and age, your login information and any other information you provide to us (collectively, "personal information"). 

The VBN also collects information you voluntarily submit about your business and its activities, including type of business, location, demographics, revenue, type of office, history, topics of interest, or other descriptive information. Further, the VBN also collects information embodied in any posts, comments, materials or other information you post, submit or upload through the VBN. 

The VBN may also on occasion request you to voluntarily submit information about other people or businesses. For example, you might be asked for the name, email address, or Facebook ID of people or businesses you know so we can inform them about the VBN, a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion or program offered on the VBN or other Visa website, or otherwise in connection with any program that Visa or its issuing financial institutions might offer. This information will also, as applicable, be subject to this privacy policy. 

Information About Your Browsing and Use of the VBN

The VBN collects non-personal information about your browsing and use of the VBN, including the information discussed below. 

The VBN uses various technologies to help manage its online advertising and communications and to enhance your experience with the VBN, including cookies, web beacons, or pixels, any or all of which may be provided by our advertising delivery, optimization or reporting partners. Web beacons (also called "pixel tags" or clear GIFs) are small strings of code placed on a web page or within an e-mail for the purpose of transferring information. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a Web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience (such as, rotating images on the home page of the VBN Website), or to provide information about any online advertisements you may have clicked on prior to your visit to the VBN. Cookies are also used to gather VBN statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the Internet provider's domain name and country of origin, and the addresses of sites visited immediately before, and after, coming to the VBN, as well as your "click stream" activity (meaning, the paths taken by visitors to the VBN as they move from page to page). We may group this information into aggregate user data in order to describe the use of the VBN to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers or other third parties, or in response to a government request. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the VBN. If you prefer, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie and privacy preferences.) 

For more information regarding third party pixels, web beacons, and cookies, or to opt out of targeted advertisements delivered by our advertising delivery partners, go to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

None of the information collected through VBN’s statistical reporting technologies is associated with your personally identifiable information; it is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate, unless you have selected to opt-in to participate in an email program. An email program consists of you voluntarily registering your VBN user account to receive periodic emails or messages from Visa. 

Information we collect through VBN statistical reporting technologies may be used to enhance the VBN in ways like these: 

* Arrange the VBN in the most user-friendly way;   
* Customize your VBN experience;   
* Provide content, information, and advertising that is most useful to you and other VBN users;  
* Communicate special offers and featured items to you, (if you choose to receive such notices); and  
* Respond to your questions or suggestions.  

Submitting Information to Third Party Sites

When you register for a third-party website or social network, such as creating a Facebook or Twitter account, you are submitting your personal information to the third party who operates the site or network, not to Visa. The VBN integrates certain information from these other websites and platforms, which may include information from your account, profile, or activities from such third-party sites. Visa does not store or retain this information. Finally, when you visit the VBN Applications, third parties with whom the VBN Applications interact may use certain information related to your visit to enable your use of the VBN and to render the pages that you visit. These third parties may also employ cookies to store certain information from your browser during the time you are visiting or logged in to their sites, including through the VBN Applications. 

All of the above types of information are subject to the privacy policies of the applicable third-party website. 

##### Information posted to VBN

You should be aware that any information you post can be read, collected or used by other users of the VBN or visitors to the VBN Website, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages or used in an otherwise unauthorized manner. We cannot be responsible for any personal Information you choose to post through those means and we recommend careful consideration before you post such information.

Cookies set by Google Analytics do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you. None of the information collected through Google Analytics is associated with you as an individual; it is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate, unless you have selected to opt-in to participate in an email program, which consists of you voluntarily registering your VBN user account to receive periodic emails or messages from Visa. 

##### Sweepstakes, contests, games, and surveys 

From time to time, Visa may conduct sweepstakes, contests, games or other promotions, and also conduct surveys through the VBN. If you choose to participate--unless otherwise noted in the applicable rules, terms and conditions, or disclaimers--we may use the information you provide in connection with the admin of the applicable promotion, including for selection and notification of sweepstakes or contest winners and for creation of new promotions, and/or to publish survey results in aggregate on the VBN. Except where necessary to administer a sweepstakes, contest, game or other promotion or survey, unless set forth in the rules or terms applicable to such promotion or survey, unless you have otherwise agreed, or unless required by law, we will not share or publish any response you give connected to your name or address. We will hold these responses only as anonymous statistics. 

##### Email, mailing lists, and other services 

When you send us an email or a message through the VBN, we use your email address or VBN account ID to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question. We store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will not use your email address or VBN account ID to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with, or sell it to, anyone else for such use, other than as specified in this policy. 

When you request information or services, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information and/or services you've requested until you ask us to stop (by using the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on each email and/or the website where you signed up and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. Other than as set forth herein, we will not use your email address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited message or information (unless the message or information is part of the service you are requesting).

##### Affiliated businesses and links to other sites 

We work closely with our affiliated businesses, vendors, partners, issuers and merchants, many of which have links within the VBN. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the VBN to another Web site, this privacy policy no longer applies. Your browsing and interaction on any third party's Web site, including any Web site that has a link on the VBN, is subject to the rules and policies of that Web site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the Web site you visit to better understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information. 

##### Our policy regarding selling or renting of personal information 

The VBN policy is simple: we do not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. However, in the event that Visa undergoes a business transfer, reorganization, or bankruptcy (discussed below in "Business Transfers"), your personal information may be transferred to a new entity. 

##### Agents, Partners, and Vendors 

We may work with other companies and individuals to perform services on behalf of Visa, such as (1) administering special reward or other programs affiliated with Visa, or sweepstakes, contests and other promotions, (2) sending emails, (3) providing marketing assistance, and (4) analyzing data and providing data support. Some of these companies and individuals will have access to the personal information necessary to perform their services, but will not be permitted to use it for any other purpose. 

##### Banners and other advertisements on the Visa Business Network 

The VBN may display banners and other advertisements that may be placed by third parties. Such advertisers may collect non-personally identifiable information when you click or scan one of their advertisements by placing cookies on your computer or by using other technology. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any such third parties. In addition, we may share aggregate information about our visitors to third-party ad servers or potential advertisers in order to provide advertisements on the VBN about products and services that may be of interest to you.

##### Business transfers

If a third party acquires all or substantially all of our assets, your personal information, aggregated information, and any other information that we have collected on the VBN may be transferred to such third party as part of our business assets. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered one of our assets and may be sold or transferred to third parties. 

##### Disclosure of personal information for legal purposes and protection of Visa and others 

We reserve the right to share your personal information with third parties if required to do so by law, or if we believe such action is necessary in order to: (1) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served upon us; (2) protect or defend our legal rights or property, the VBN or its users; or (3) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of any of the terms and conditions for using the VBN. 

#### CHOICE

##### How you can decide what messages you'll receive from us

If you choose to receive them, we may periodically send you email messages or messages within the VBN describing promotional or marketing offers related to the VBN or otherwise related to Visa or its member financial institutions (collectively, "Promotional Communications"). You can choose at any time what sorts of Promotional Communications you would like to receive by changing the settings within your VBN page. If you do not explicitly choose to receive Promotional Communications, the only email messages you will receive from Visa will be (a) responses to an inquiries that you send us; and/or (b) email messages in connection with updates, new features or other similar information regarding the VBN, the VBN Website and/or the VBN Facebook Application. 

#### ACCESS AND DATA RETENTION

##### How to update, correct, or delete your personal information

You can access and modify your personal information stored on the VBN, such as your name, company name, phone number, email address, and mailing address, by making changes to your VBN profile. To modify or delete personal information related to an email program, simply follow the instructions included in your email and we will make any appropriate requested changes. 

We retain information provided to us indefinitely unless otherwise stated. We will keep some personal information you have requested to remove for the following purposes: 

* Troubleshoot problems   
* Assist with investigations   
* Enforce VBN rules   
* Comply with legal requirements   

Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will always be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. 

#### SECURITY

##### How we protect the security of your personal information

The security of your personal information is very important to us, and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While we cannot guarantee absolute security of your personal information, Visa and its providers employ many different security techniques to protect personal data against loss, misuse, alteration, and unauthorized access. As stated elsewhere in this policy, however, if you access the VBN through the VBN Applications, including the VBN Facebook Application, third parties may also have possession of some parts of your personal information related to your account with that third party (not your VBN account), so it is important that you review the third party's privacy policy, which also applies to your information. 

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE AND RECOURSE

##### Changes to the Visa Business Network privacy policy

This privacy policy was posted on May 28, 2009. Visa reserves the right to change, modify, or amend this policy at any time in accordance with applicable laws. Please also read and familiarize yourself with the Visa Business Network Terms of Use, the [Facebook Terms of Use](https://www.facebook.com/terms.php), the [Facebook Platform Application Terms of Use](http://developers.facebook.com/user_terms.php), the [Facebook Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php), the [Twitter Terms of Service](http://www.twitter.com/tos), the [Twitter Privacy Policy](http://www.twitter.com/privacy), and the terms of use and privacy policies for any third-party websites or platforms that are accessible through a VBN Application. Visa takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. Visa may occasionally update this privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates. 

##### How to contact Visa regarding your concerns and questions

Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any services related to the VBN, you consent to let us process this information in the United States as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. 

If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about Visa's privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to contact us through the VBN, email us at [askvisausa@visa.com](mailto:askvisausa@visa.com?cc=support@visabusinessnetwork.zendesk.com) or write to us at: 

Visa Inc.   
P.O. Box 194607   
San Francisco, California 94119-4607   
Attention: Visa Business Network Webmaster   

Should you have a dispute regarding this privacy policy, we will resolve it and take any remedial action as we reasonably determine in our discretion and in accordance with applicable laws.
